everybody welcome back to the studio I'm
모두가 난 스튜디오에 다시 오신 것을 환영합니다
Robbie and my web show is triple W
로비와 웹은 트리플 W
category 5 TV this is the studio that we
카테고리 5 TV이 스튜디오는 우리가
produce category 5 technology TV in and
카테고리 5 기술 TV를 생산하고
we are in the midst of setting up an
우리는습니다 설정의 중간에 있습니다
HDMI clean output on a d50 100 that's a
d50 100의 HDMI 클린 출력
camera that's available quite cheap 350
꽤 싸게 이용할 수있는 카메라 350
bucks kind of thing on the cheap
싸구려 물건을 사다.
so you definitely want to check this out
그래서 이것을 확실히 확인 하고 싶습니다.
if you're looking for a cheap solution
저렴한 솔루션을 찾고 있다면
for good quality video now just so you
지금은 좋은 품질의 비디오를위한 당신 때문에
know we've got it working as you know
우리가 알고있는 대로 일하고 있다는 것을 알아라.
from the last time that we that we were
우리가 마지막으로했던 때 부터
talking I'm going to show you all about
이야기 나는 여러분 모두에 대해 보여 드리겠습니다
how we do that now I I'm gonna be
우리가 어떻게하는지 지금 나는있을거야.
putting together a show I just wanna let
난 그냥 싶어하자 쇼를 함께 넣어
you know right off the bat we're putting
우리가 쥐고있는 방망이 바로 알지.
together a new show called the show show
함께 쇼 쇼라는 새로운 쇼
and the whole purpose of the show show
쇼 쇼의 목적은
and the whole play on words there with
그리고 거기에 있는 모든 말은
the dual use of the word show is that
쇼라는 단어 의 이중 사용은
it's a show about how to create web cast
웹 캐스트를 만드는 방법에 대한 쇼입니다.
how to create your own show it is
자신 만의 쇼 를 만드는 방법
applicable to churches it's applicable
해당 교회에 적용 가능
to to small businesses it's applicable
적용 가능한 중소기업에 이르기 까지
to teachers and students alike I mean
교사와 학생들에게 모두 내 말은
anyone really who wants who's got
누가 진짜로 원하는 사람인가?
something to say and wants to create a
뭔가 말과를 만들려고합니다
show the show show is definitely gonna
show show가 분명하게 나타날 것을 보여 주라.
be for you so if you haven't already got
너를 위해서라면 너는 이미
it make sure you install the
그것은 당신이 설치되었는지 확인하십시오 .
category-five TV roku channel on your
카테고리 5 TV 로쿠 채널
Roku device a quick link for that is cat
Roku 장치에 대한 빠른 링크는 고양이입니다.
v dot TV slash roku channel and of
v 도트 TV 슬래시 로쿠 채널 및
course if you already got it awesome
물론 당신은 이미 멋진 가지고있는 경우
because that's where you're gonna find
그게 네가 찾을 수있는 곳 이기 때문에
it category five TVs branching out into
카테고리 5 개의 TV가
a whole bunch of other shows not just
다른 많은 프로그램들이
category five technology TV but also the
카테고리 5 기술 TV뿐만 아니라
show show try it buy it we've also got
show show it it we 've also 그것을 사세요.
the nature to the nature sounds of
성격에 자연의 소리
Ontario Canada there I mean some
캐나다 온타리오가 좀 의미
interesting stuff and it really helps us
흥미로운 것들 이며 정말 도움 이 됩니다.
to branch out into new areas so that
그래서 새로운 영역으로 넓히기하기
said this is backstage passes is behind
이것이 무대 뒤 통로 라고 말했다.
the scenes so I'm allowed to take you on
장면은 그래서 나는에 당신을 데려 갈 수있어
a tour of you know you can see how
당신의 여행은 어떻게 볼 수 있는지 알고 있습니다.
things happen backstage and we're very
일 무대 발생하고 우리는 매우있어
very casual because I'm here my kids are
내가 여기 있기 때문에 캐주얼이 아주 좋다.
here you can't see them on that camera
여기 당신은 그 카메라에서 그들을 볼 수 없습니다.
but if well there you go you know that
그러나 잘 거기에 있다면 당신은 당신이 그것을 알게됩니다.
it is in fact a DSLR there they are
실제로 DSLR입니다.
if I can focus hey kids turn around and
내가 초점을 맞출 수 있다면 헤이 아이들이 주변에 돌고
wave hey yeah they're playing Sega
웨이브 헤이 그래 그들은 세가 연주있어
Genesis
창세기
because it's awesome that's our cross
그것이 우리의 십자가 에서 굉장 하기 때문에
promo for try buy it
구매를 위한 프로모션
Sasha show she's doing a review on a
사샤는 그녀 가
Sega Genesis unit that has a whole bunch
한 무리의 세가 창세기
of games built in bringing back the
다시 데려에 내장 된 게임의
old-school retro game and I love it
구식 복고풍 게임과 나는 그것을 사랑한다
so the kids are the kids are actually
그래서 아이들 은 실제로 아이들 입니다.
really really enjoying some of those
정말로 그 중 일부를 즐기고 있습니다.
old-school games so I love that it takes
낡은 학교 게임 그래서 나는 그것을 좋아한다.
me back okay so today this is part 2 of
나 다시 괜찮아. 오늘이 부분은 2 부.
our DSLR series really really quick
DSLR 시리즈는 정말 빠릅니다.
backstage pass stuff and again this
무대 뒤에서 물건을주고 다시
stuff is going to be covered on the show
물건 쇼에 적용 할 것입니다
show as well so we're gonna do more in
보여줄뿐만 아니라 우리는 더 많은 것을 할 것 입니다.
depth and show you how it works but I
깊이 있고 어떻게 작동하는지 보여 주지만 나는
want to give you a sneak peek because I
너 한테 몰래 들어 줄래 ?
know you've been following on YouTube
당신이 YouTube에서 서비스 된 것을 알고있다
and through the forums over at
이상 포럼에서 통해
Telestream so and I appreciate your
Telestream과 내가 고맙게 생각 합니다.
interaction as well it's been nice
상호 작용도 좋았어요.
talking to some of you and and learning
당신과 학습의 몇 가지 이야기
kind of what you know what you're gonna
네가 뭘할지 알지 ?
be using this for and and a couple of
and를 사용하여
you have already bought addy 5100 reason
당신은 이미 addy 5100 이유를 구입했습니다.
that I've chosen this camera is because
내가이 카메라를 선택한 이유는
it is so cheap and because our friends
너무 싸고 우리 친구들이
at Nite con hacker have already cracked
Nite 사기꾼 해커가 이미 금이 갔다.
a lot of the stuff that has to do with
함께 할 수있는 물건을 많이
the firmware so that opens it up to
그래서 펌웨어는 그것을 열어
doing some things that are not typically
일반적으로
available on a cheap camera so you see
당신이 볼 수 있도록 싼 카메라를 볼 수 있습니다
that I've got HDMI output this is that
나는 HDMI 출력을 가지고 있다.
25 foot cable that we had in the first
우리가 처음으로 가지고 있던 25 피트 케이블
part of this this segment and on there
이 부분과이 부분의 일부
I've just got the consumer camera so if
나는 방금 소비자 카메라를 가지고있다. if
I want to show you what what I've got
내가 가진 걸 보여주고 싶다.
going on there's the camera that I'm
거기에가는 난 카메라
actually on right now and then this is
실제로 지금에 다음이이다
the D 5100 how am i pulling it in
D 5100은 어때 ?
alright so we looked at it last week you
알았어. 그래서 지난 주에 너를 보았다.
know that it was stretched out I talked
내가 뻗어 있다는 것을 알았다. 나는 이야기했다.
to Simeon pilgrim he's one of the guys
시므온 순례자에게 그는 남자들 중 하나입니다.
at the forefront of the Nikon hacker
니콘 해커의 선두에
group and they create the hacks the the
그룹 과 그들은 해킹을 만듭니다
firmware that allows us to break some of
우리가 몇 가지를 깰 수있는 펌웨어
the stuff in the camera not not in the
카메라에서 물건을하지하지에
traditional sense of breaking it like
그것을 깨는 전통적인 감각
you dropped it in it's shattered but to
너는 그것에 떨어 뜨렸다.
crack the the codes that allow us to do
우리가 할 수 있는 코드 를 해독하십시오.
clean hdmi output for example you notice
당신이 알 예를 들어, 깨끗한 HDMI 출력
that all the on-screen stuff is gone
모든 화면의 물건을 사라된다
yeah you can't normally do that right
예, 당신은 정상적으로 그렇게 할 수 없습니다.
you plug this in and you're gonna have
이걸 연결하면
you're gonna have all that stuff on the
당신은 모든 그 물건을 가지고거야
screen so okay you got a little bit of a
화면이 너무 좋아요 .
glimpse there but just to show you that
거기에서 흘끗 보아라. 그러나 단지 당신에게 그것을 보여주기 위해
is Telestream Wirecast okay so I've got
Telestream Wirecast입니다. 괜찮습니다.
Telestream Wirecast version 6 and you'll
Telestream Wirecast 버전 6을 사용하면
see what I'm talking about with
내가 함께 무슨 말인지 참조
autofocus my autofocus is going crazy
자동 초점 내 자동 초점이 미쳐 버렸다.
right and you also see that with the
맞습니다.
Nikon hacker firmware I'm still
Nikon 해커 펌웨어
stretched out now Simeon commented on
시므온이 지금 뻗어있다.
our YouTube channel
YouTube 채널
Linux tech show that that's in fact
리눅스 기술 쇼는 사실 그것이 사실입니다.
because the camera sensor grabs the
카메라 센서를 잡고 있기 때문에
image a little bit differently than say
말을 다르게보다 이미지 조금
a camcorder would because a camcorders
캠코더하고자했다 캠코더 때문에
going to capture the 1920 by 1080 and
1080 년까지 1920 년을
send it directly over the HDMI now this
이제 HDMI를 통해 직접 보내십시오.
they're trying to pull as much data from
그들은 많은 데이터를
the sensor as possible and then give it
센서를 가능한 한 다음 제공하십시오.
to you and it's not a sixteen over nine
당신과는 아홉 열 여섯 아니다에
true frame so that's why I end up
진정한 프레임 그래서 내가 결국
gaining twenty pounds on this camera I
이 카메라 I에 20 파운드를 얻고
look much better on this camera thank
이 카메라로 훨씬 더보기 좋게 감사합니다.
you very much Simeon Pilgrim trying to
너 시므온 순례자는
make me look fat I say if I wanted to
내가 뚱뚱해 보이게하고 싶다면 내가 원하면 내가 말한다.
gain 20 pounds I would do it by bacon
20 파운드를 얻는다. 나는 베이컨에 의해 그것을 할 것이다.
not by firmware okay so what am I gonna
펌웨어가 아닌 , 좋아, 그럼 내가 뭘 할거야?
do well you heard me mention a couple of
너 나 한테 몇 마디 들었어.
times that we're using made well cards
우리가 사용하고있는 시간 은 좋은 카드 를 만들었습니다.
and that there is good rate good reason
좋은 비율 좋은 이유가있다
for that
그에 대한
first of all okay so this camera is
우선 이 카메라 가 좋아.
going into a Blackmagic intensity Pro
Blackmagic intensity Pro에 들어가기
that's what I you know have been using
그게 네가 아는 거야.
previously to picking up a mage well
이전에는 마법사를 잘 잡으러왔다.
card so and it's an okay card but to be
카드 그래서 그것은 괜찮은 카드지만 될
honest it's very very limiting I don't
아주 아주 제한하는 것 솔직히 난 몰라
know if you've used one I'm gonna pull
네가 하나를 사용 했다면 내가 당길거야.
up Telestream Wirecast on the screen
화면에 Telestream Wirecast를 올리십시오.
here I'm going to pull up my settings
여기 내 설정을 끌어 올께.
for that particular card so let's bring
그 특별한 카드 때문에 가져다 드리겠습니다.
up my intensity Pro so here we go and
내 강도 Pro를 그래서 여기에 우리가 가서
you can see all the different capture
당신 은 모든 다른 캡처를 볼 수 있습니다.
devices that I have so here's my
내가 가지고있는 장치 들은 여기에있다.
intensity Pro looks fine right you've
강도 Pro는 잘 했어.
really just got you know the ability to
정말로 방금 당신 이
set to specific resolutions which is
어떤 특정 해상도로 설정
fine but the problem with that is that
좋습니다.하지만 그 문제 는
if you step outside of that it's gonna
당신은 거의 그 이외의 스텝 경우
just give you a black screen so that's a
그는 그래서 당신에게 검은 화면을 제공
problem now this will pull from the D
문제는 이제 D 에서 끌어낼 것입니다 .
5100 however you notice what do I got
5100 그러나 당신 은 내가 무엇을 얻었는지 알아 차린다.
I've got the ability to change the
나는 능력을 바꾼다.
resolution frame rate I've got the
해상도 프레임 속도
ability to deandre lace or not and to
레이스를하거나하지 않을 수있는 능력
apply that's it that's lame then that
그것을 적용하면 절름발이입니다.
sucks I want to show you why the mage
왜 마술사인지 왜 보여줄 까?
well card
우물 카드
blows black magic out of the water okay
괜찮 물 밖으로 검은 마법을 불어
so I'm gonna switch shots here to this
여기에 총을 이걸로 바꿀거야.
camera yeah okay so see I'm stretched
카메라 그래 좋아, 그래서 내가 뻗어있어 참조하십시오
out I'm gonna switch over to Telestream
나가 Telestream로 전환 할거야.
Wirecast I'm gonna bring up the source
와이어 캐스트 나는 정보원을 불러올거야.
for this particular camera and this is
이 특정 카메라는 여기에 있습니다.
on the the mage well card now I've put
마술사 우물 카드에 이제 놓았습니다.
in the 4k capture card that's the X I
4K 캡처 카드에 X I가 있어요.
100 de and it's HDMI video capture
100 de 및 그것의 HDMI 비디오 캡처
using yeah it's over HDMI let's see what
예를 통해 HDMI를 통해 HDMI를 통해
what's going on there yeah okay so I've
거기에 무슨 일이있어 그래, 그래, 그래.
got frame and yeah let's see if I can
프레임이 있고 그래, 내가 볼 수 있는지 보자.
bring it up here sources show source
여기 소스를 가져 와서 소스를 보여줘.
settings and there's my mate well card
설정 및 내 친구 카드 잘 있어요.
what is going on here oh I'm sorry
여기에 무슨 일이 일어나고 있니? 미안해.
haha like HDMI there's two inputs on
HDMI와 같은 하하 거기에 두 개의 입력이 있습니다.
there there's the one that I'm actually
실제로 해요 하나가있다
using whoops okay so you see I'm pulling
후프를 사용하여 좋아, 그래서 내가 당기고있어.
in at 720p I could be pulling in at 1080
720p에서 나는 1080에서 당길 수 있었다.
and of course if my source allowed it I
그리고 물론 내 소스가 그것을 허용한다면
could actually pull in at 4k because
실제로 4k에서 끌어 들일 수 있기 때문에
this card supports up to 4k and that's
이 카드는 최대 4K 지원 그건
the idea so you notice okay device
아이디어 그래서 당신은 괜찮은 장치를 통지
deinterlacing that's obviously a part of
드 인터 레이싱 은 분명히
it if you've got an interlaced source
인터레이스 된 소스 가 있다면
I'm using the 720p output patch which is
720p 출력 패치를 사용하고 있습니다.
progressive so I don't need to use the
프로그레시브 방식 으로 사용할 필요가 없습니다 .
interlacing and I like that because it's
인터 레이싱과 내가 좋아하는 그이기 때문에 그
gonna reduce my CPU usage because it's
CPU 사용량이 줄어들어
already progressive I don't have to
이미 진보적인데 나는 할 필요가 없다.
de-ice the video which takes more CPU
더 많은 CPU를 사용 하는 비디오를 제거합니다.
power so that's why I'm doing 1280 by
힘이 그래서 내가 왜 1280을하고있는거야?
720 and no device DeAndre lacing okay so
720 및 장치 없음 DeAndre 레이싱 괜찮아요.
now here's where the mage well card
지금 여기 어디 마술사 잘 카드입니다
shows off all right you ready for this
너는 이것에 대한 준비가 되어 있어.
configure now you see that my face is
지금 내 얼굴이 보이는지 구성 해라.
frozen that's okay you can still hear me
냉동 괜찮아요 당신은 아직도 나에게들을 수 있습니다
now look at what we've got here
지금 우리가 가진 것을 보아라.
HDMI blah blah blah okay here you go it
HDMI ㅋ ㅋㅋㅋ 좋아, 여기 있어.
knows that it's pulling in a particular
그것이 특정한 것을 끌어 당기는 것을 압니다.
type of video it knows that we've got
우리가 알고있는 비디오 유형
750 lines off of the capture card that's
캡처 카드의 750 라인
also seems to be pulling 60 frames per
또한 60 프레임 당 당기는 것 같습니다.
second and it's showing as a progressive
제하며 진보적으로 나타내는 것
scan that's what the P means so HDMI
스캔은 P가 의미하는 것입니다. 그래서 HDMI
input with audio but we don't use the
오디오가 포함 된 입력은 사용하지만
audio off of that so it's auto selected
오디오가 꺼져있어 자동 선택됨
and us picked up on that camera and it
우리가 그 카메라를 집어 들고
knows that that's what it is so you
그게 니가 그렇게 생각하는거야.
notice what the mange well car gives us
쥐똥 거리는 차가 우리에게주는 것을 알아 차려라.
is it gives us the ability to change the
그것이 우리에게 능력을 바꿀 수있는
way it crops and fills the screen
그것은 작물을 만들고 화면을 채 웁니다.
huh so typically it's gonna be keep
그게 전형적으로 계속 될거야 .
aspect ratio fill border with black
검은 색 테두리 비율 채우기
that's the typical behavior so in our
그 전형적인 행동의 너무 우리
case then we would have black borders
그렇다면 우리 는 검은 색 테두리를 가질 것입니다.
but what I want to do is I want to
하지만 내가하고 싶은 일은 내가 원하는거야.
actually fill the image output and just
실제로 이미지 출력을 채우고
and watch what happens if I increase the
내가 그걸 늘리면 어떻게 될지 지켜봐 .
width let's just go way up there so see
너는 저기 로 올라가 자.
what's happening to my resolution 1400
내 결의안 1400에 무슨 일이 일어나고있는거야?
by 720 is probably about where I'm going
아마 720에 이르러 내가 갈 곳 이 어쩌면
look at this okay 13 90 by 720 is this
(720)에 의해이 좋아 13 90이되어 봐
best I can high as I can go so now I'm
나는 내가 지금 갈 수 있는만큼 최고 일 수 있다.
gonna fill the output image and then I'm
출력 이미지를 채우면 나는
gonna hit OK and that's gonna get rid of
OK를 치면 그걸 없애 버릴거야.
the stretching notice that so I've got a
스트레칭 알림 그래서 나는
black bar over there but I can get that
저기에 검은 색 막대가 있지만 나는 그것을 얻을 수 있습니다.
out in in
안으로
Wirecast I'll show you how to do that so
Wirecast 나는 어떻게 그렇게하는지 보여줄거야.
go back to configure here I want to show
다시 구성하려면 여기 로 돌아가서 표시하고 싶습니다.
you why else okay remember that the
당신은 왜 다른 괜찮 기억
Blackmagic intensity card had no
Blackmagic 강도 카드가 없었습니다.
settings whatsoever
무엇이든지 설정
look at that ha ha the mage well card
저것을 봐 하하 마법사 좋은 카드
lets you adjust in live mode your RGB
라이브 모드에서 RGB를 조정할 수 있습니다.
brightness and contrast of each channel
각 채널 의 밝기 및 대비
also lets you look at this hue and
또한 이 색조 를 볼 수 있습니다.
saturation gamma you can set your white
채도 감마를 사용하면 흰색을 설정할 수 있습니다.
balance and everything if I guess like I
균형과 모든 것은 내가처럼 생각하는 경우
mean it's all there right just like a
그게 모두 바로 거기에 있다는 것을 의미합니다 .
typical driver would allow you to I
전형적인 운전자는 나 에게 당신 을 허용 할 것이다.
white balance I see is is grayed out I'm
내가 볼 수있는 화이트 밸런스가 회색으로 표시됩니다.
not sure why that is but you get a lot
확실하지 즉하지만 당신은 많이 얻을 이유
more options with the mage well card
마법사 웰 카드로 더 많은 옵션 제공
than you do with the Blackmagic
당신이 블랙 매직보다
intensity Pro so this gives me the
intensity Pro를 사용 하면
ability to change the saturation for
에 대한 채도를 변경하는 기능
example change the hue get it a little
예를 들어 색조를 조금 바꾸면됩니다 .
bit brighter or darker depending on the
조금 더 밝거나 어둡게
environment directly from the driver so
환경 에서 드라이버를 직접
now that I've done that okay see what
지금은 괜찮 무엇을 볼 수 있다고했던 것을
I've got now I can switch back to my
나는 다시 전환 할 수 있습니다 지금있어 내
camera source and you'll see that I've
카메라 소스와 당신은 내가
got a black bar over there but the
저기에 검은 색 막대가 있지만
picture looks great I'm not stretched
그림이 멋지다 나는 뻗어 있지 않다.
out I don't look fat well at least no
나는 적어도 뚱뚱해 보이지 않는다.
fatter than I do on this camera anyway
어쨌든이 카메라에 할 오르게보다
alright now watch what I'm gonna do I'm
좋아, 지금 내가 뭘할지 지켜봐.
gonna bring back up Telestream Wirecast
Telestream Wirecast를 다시 불러 올거야.
bring up my shot there we go this is so
이 때문에 우리가 갈이 내 총을 가지고
easy there's my shot right I'm just
내 발소리가 쉽다. 난 그냥
gonna hole in the wrong key yeah
잘못된 키 거 구멍 그래
holding my Alt key and then I can just
내 Alt 키 를 누른 상태에서 방금 할 수 있습니다.
kind of zoom in just ever so slightly
조금만 확대해서 보아라.
there you go and I mean it's not gonna
거기 당신은 가고 나는 않을거야 의미
be lossy enough that you're gonna that
네가 그렇게 할만 큼 손실이있다.
you're gonna care okay so I've just
니가 걱정할거야, 그래서 난 그냥
gotten rid of that black bar on the side
그 검은 색 바를 없애 버렸습니다.
there we go
우리는 거기에 갈
now there you go perfect now see the
지금 너 거기 완벽 해 이제 너 보고
autofocus going crazy now I'm gonna turn
이제 미친 듯이 자동 초점이 바뀝니다.
off auto focus that we don't do that I'm
우리가하지 않는 자동 초점을 내가 벗어났다.
gonna get a nice focus there look at how
어떻게 거기에 좋은 초점을 얻을 거야
I can blur out the background with the
나는 배경 을 흐리게 할 수있다 .
we've got a Dee 5100 looking beautiful
우리는 아름다운 5100을보고있다.
on Telestream Wirecast and the way to do
Telestream Wirecast 및 방법
that is with a mage well capture card
마법사 와 잘 어울리는 카드
now that's again I'm using the 4k card
이제 다시 4k 카드를 사용하고 있습니다.
and it goes it's down we're compatible
그리고 그것은 우리가 호환되는 내려 갑니다
to any resolution that's why we wanted
우리가 원했던 모든 해결책에
it because we are gonna be also
우리 가 또한 있기 때문에
demonstrating using the gh4 and a couple
gh4와 한 쌍을 사용하여 시연
other cameras as well in 4k mode with
다른 카메라 뿐만 아니라 4K 모드에서
live Digital cropping so that you can
디지털 방식으로 자르기
get 720 and 1080 P frames and move them
720 및 1080 P 프레임 가져 오기 및 이동
around on a 4k cam on a 4k source so
4k 소스 의 4k 캠에서
that's that's why we need this card but
그것이 우리가이 카드 가 필요한 이유입니다.
look at that look at how gorgeous that
얼마나 멋 있는지 봐.
looks I don't know if my focus is
내 초점이 맞는지 모르겠다.
perfect I'm only looking at the preview
완벽한 나는 미리보기 만보고있다.
window over here right but that to me
여기 오른쪽 창문 은 나 한테는 그렇다.
looks pretty darn good so we're gonna
꽤 좋아 보인다. 그래서 우리는
want to change our let's see up on my
우리 의 변화를 보고 싶다.
camera here I'm gonna change camera
카메라는 여기 내가 카메라를 바꿀거야
there we go okay so over here we've got
거기서 우리는 괜찮아. 그래서 여기에 우리가 있어.
a an exposure button I can hold that in
노출 버튼 난에 그를 저장할 수
with the hacked firmware I can hold in
내가 보유 할 수있는 해킹 된 펌웨어
the exposure button and then I can dial
노출 버튼을 누른 다음 전화를 걸 수 있습니다.
the wheel and I can actually change the
바퀴 와 나는 실제로 그것을 바꿀 수있다.
exposure on the fly look at that okay so
날아 오르는 표정은 그 정도로 좋아 보인다.
you can get that really really nice mix
정말 멋진 믹스를 얻을 수 있습니다.
the nice color the nice exposure which
멋진 색 좋은 노출
is going to affect your color obviously
분명히 당신의 색깔에 영향을 줄 것입니다.
and that is again provided with one of
그리고 그것은 다시
the Nikon hack or firmware hacks so now
니콘 해킹이나 펌웨어 해킹이 지금 당장
I'm still holding in that that button
나는 아직도 그 버튼을 잡고있다.
I'm gonna hit the lock button for auto
자동 잠금 버튼을 누르면됩니다.
exposure now my exposure is locked and
이제 노출이 고정 되고
it's gonna stay like that so even if I
그것은거야 그래서 심지어 내가 만약 그 머물 것
even if I go tour I don't have all the
내가 투어를가 더라도 나는 모든 것을 가지고 있지 않습니다.
lights on but there's a light on over
에 빛하지만 빛이 이상에있다
and it's not changing my exposure that
내 노출 을 바꾸지 않아.
my exposure still stays real real nice
내 노출은 여전히 ​​진짜 진짜 멋지 네요.
welcome to the studio by the way here we
스튜디오에 오신 것을 환영합니다.
are at this is the studio for category 5
카테고리 5 의 스튜디오입니다.
there's a chroma key room we've got the
우리가 가지고 있는 크로마 키 룸 이 있습니다.
interview area over there notice what I
인터뷰 영역은저기서 내가
can do with the focus right our audio
우리 오디오에 집중할 수 있습니다.
rack which you're going to see on the
당신이에 보게 될 것 랙
show show you're gonna see all this
당신은거야 쇼 쇼는이 모든 것을 볼 수
stuff and kids over there in what is
물건 과 거기의 어린이는 무엇에있다.
normally our audience seating when we're
일반적으로 우리 청중이 앉아있을 때
when we're live on the air but of course
우리는 공기에 있지만, 물론 라이브있을 때
again this is kind of a backstage view
다시 이것은 일종의 무대 뒤에서 볼 수 있습니다.
just for you so I hope that you'll
당신은 그래서 당신이거야 희망 단지에 대한
you'll watch the show show it's gonna be
너는 쇼가 될거야 .
a lot of fun it's gonna be really
정말 재미있을거야.
excited it's gonna be not quite as
정말 흥분하지 않을거야.
casual as this a little bit more
이 조금 더 캐주얼
professionalism not not so much the
전문성이 그렇게 많지는 않다.
handheld shots but I'll probably use a
핸드 헬드 샷을 사용하지만 아마도
tripod for most of it but it is going to
그것의 대부분을위한 삼각 그러나 그것은에 가고있다.
have the same kind of you know we're
너와 똑같은 종류의 우리를 알라.
teaching and showing you how we do
우리가 어떻게하는지 가르치고 보여 줍니다.
things over here and some of the cool
여기있는 것들 과 시원한 것들
stuff that we're going to be able to do
우리는 할 수있을거야 물건
using you know everything from DSLRs GPS
DSLR GPS 에서 모든 것을 아는 사용
LRS I've got a see that iPod behind me
LRS 저 뒤에있는 iPod을 보았습니다.
an iPod Touch we're going to be using as
우리가 사용하게 될 iPod Touch
a live camera source on Telestream
Telestream의 라이브 카메라 소스
Wirecast I know you know it can be done
와이어 캐스트 나는 당신이 그것이 끝날 수 있다는 것을 압니다.
we're gonna show you some of the really
우리는 너 에게 정말로 어떤 것을 보여줄거야.
cool things that you can do with that
당신이 그걸로 할 수있는 멋진 것들
kind of setup that's all happening on
모든 일이 벌어지고있는 종류의 설치
the show show so really this is all I
쇼 쇼 정말 정말이 모든 것입니다.
need to show you for the HDMI thing I
의 HDMI 일이 내가 당신을 보여줄 필요
mean did you think it was going to only
당신 은 그것이 단지
take two quick little behind-the-scenes
배후에 두 가지 간단한 것을 가져 가라.
videos but that that's it that works and
동영상을 재생할 수 있습니다.
it looks great thank you so much to the
정말 대단히 감사합니다 .
guys over at at Nikon hacker and thank
니콘 해커 와 감사의 인사들
you to you for for watching I'll remind
제가 알려 드리겠습니다 시청을위한 당신에게 당신
you to to check out our show
당신이 우리 쇼를 체크 아웃하려면
category-five technology TV check out
카테고리 -5 기술 TV 체크 아웃
our channel category-five TV and our
채널 카테고리 - 5 개의 TV와
website category v dot TV of course but
웹 사이트 카테고리 v 점 TV 물론
on our channel you can pick up all of
우리의 채널에 당신은 모두를 선택할 수 있습니다
our shows including the backstage pass
무대 뒤 통과를 포함한 우리 쇼
features and all that kind of stuff so
기능과 모든 종류의 물건 그래서
I'm excited about this that looks good I
내가 좋은 I를 보이는 이것에 대해 흥분
hope that we're gonna be able to launch
우리가 시작할 수 있기를 바랍니다.
this on on the show in the next couple
다음 몇 쇼에이에
of weeks let's switch back over here you
몇주 만에 다시 너에게로 돌아 가자.
can see I'm using the 1855 millimeter
내가 1855 밀리미터를 사용 하고 있음을 볼 수 있습니다.
lens on the camera right now and just to
지금 당장 카메라에있는 렌즈 를
answer the question that has been asked
질문 된 질문에 대답 한다.
we've got live view going out over HDMI
우리는 HDMI를 통해 외출 라이브 뷰를 가지고
right so you see on the on the
당신은에에 볼 권리 있도록
lcd there is no there's nothing on it
LCD 거기에 아무것도 없다 더있다
when we're when we're doing this through
우리 가이 일을 할 때
Telestream Wirecast now that's what the
Telestream Wirecast는 이제 이것이
1080 patch I'm interested to see and
내가보고 관심 1080 패치
we'll do this on the show show we'll
우리는 쇼 쇼에서 이것을 할 것입니다.
test it with the different patches
다른 패치로 테스트 해라.
oh no I'm using the 720 patch am I not
오, 아니 내가 아니에요 720 패치를 사용하고 있습니다
so well we'll do some more playing
그래서 우리는 좀 더 연주 할 것입니다.
around anyways and we'll I'll show you
어쨌든 주위에 우리는 당신을 보여주지.
how to do the patches and stuff I was
패치 와 내가했던 것들을 하는 법
also talking to Simeon over at a Nikon
니콘 에서 시므온과도 얘기하고있다.
hacker and he's going to come on and
해커는 그가에 올 것와
because the question comes up you know
문제가 오기 때문에 당신은 알고있다
when I'm hacking the firmware what does
내가 펌웨어를 해킹 할 때 무슨 일을하는지
this feature do what does that feature
이 기능은 해당 기능을 수행합니다.
do I mean I look at things like the star
나는 별 같은 것을 보았다는 것을 의미합니까?
eater and while you or I may know what
당신이나 내가 무엇을 알 수있는 동안
that is somebody who's never heard of
그건 들어 본 적이없는 사람이야.
star readers before may think well what
스타 독자들은 전에는 무엇을 생각할지 모른다.
on earth why would I like what is that
지구상에 왜 나는 그게 맘 에 드는지 ?
right so we're gonna go through bullet
맞아, 총알을 통해 갈거야.
point by bullet point and say okay well
총알 지점을 가리키며 잘 말한다.
this is what this does this is what this
이것은 이것이 이것이 무엇인지에 대한 것입니다.
does so that when you build your
당신은 구축 않을 때 있도록
firmware for Nikon hacker for your
니콘 해커 용 펌웨어
camera you're gonna you're gonna know
당신이 알게 될 카메라 야.
exactly what it is that you want to
정확히 당신이 원하는 것입니다.
select so I think that's going to be a
나는 그가 될 것 같아 그렇게 선택
really good thing that's gonna be on the
거 야에있을 것 정말 좋은 일
show show and that's gonna be happening
쇼 쇼 및 그 거 일어나고 있어요
we're gonna get this thing going as soon
우리는 곧 이 일을 진행시킬거야.
as possible it's probably gonna be
가능한 한 아마있을거야.
happening within the next few weeks
앞으로 몇 주 이내에 일어나는 일
Simeon's on deck and on board so we're
시므온이 갑판 위에 있어. 그래서 우리는
gonna make that happen and that will be
거야 그렇게하고 그 것
episode number one and then you're gonna
에피소드 번호 하나 그리고 너는
see some redundant stuff that you've
당신이 가지고있는 중복 된 것들을 보아라.
seen here as well
여기서도 볼 수 있다.
with a little bit more of a professional
조금 더 전문적인
edge but I think it'll be a lot of fun
가장자리 그러나 나는 그것이 많은 재미 일 것이다라고 생각한다.
for you and we're gonna learn a lot
너와 우리는 많은 것을 배울거야.
you're gonna save a lot of time and
너는 많은 시간을 절약 할거야.
money too because it's you know I'm
돈이 너무 네가 알기 때문에 나는
gonna do all the experimenting for you
야 모든 당신을 위해 실험 않는다
and show you what works what doesn't I
내가하지 무엇을 어떤 작품을 보여
mean you might have gone out and bought
당신은 밖으로 사라와 구입했을 수도 의미
an intensity Pro card thinking oh that's
오, 그게 생각 하는 강도 프로 카드
gonna work don't do it right you saw why
너 왜 그랬는지는 제대로 알지 못해.
we're gonna use the mage well card so
마법사 우물 카드를 사용할 거야.
and that's that's gonna be nice I'm
그리고 그게 멋질 거야.
gonna love being able to adjust the
조정할 수있는 것을 좋아할거야 .
saturation because I like to bring down
내가 포기하고 싶어서 포화 상태 야.
the saturation just a little bit and to
조금만 포화 상태 로
not have to do that in post-production
포스트 프로덕션에서 그렇게 하지 않아도된다.
is beautiful you want to know what
아름답다. 너는 무엇을 알고 싶어한다.
that's gonna do this will be the final
그 거이 마지막이 될 것 할 것
thing that we're gonna do today I want
오늘 우리가 할 일은 내가 원하는 거야 .
to show you what what changing our
우리에게 무엇이 바뀌 었는지 보여주기 위해
saturation is going to do for our
채도 가 우리 를 위해 할 것입니다.
picture because you know I look super
당신 이 내가 슈퍼 볼 줄 알기 때문에 그림
bright super crisp and clear so I'm just
밝은 슈퍼 파삭 파삭하고 맑은 그래서 난 그냥
bringing up my drivers here why don't I
왜 내 운전자를 데려 오지 않는 거야?
show you bring it up I'm gonna click on
당신 이 그걸 가져다 보여줘 내가 클릭 할거야.
the right camera this time configure and
이번에 는 올바른 카메라를 구성하고
then go over here to video proc amp
그런 다음 비디오 proc amp 로 이동 하십시오.
and let's see if I can bring down my
내가 내 얼굴을 내릴 수 있는지 보자.
saturation down to let's do 85% just to
포화 상태에서 85 % 로
see what that looks like
그 모습을 볼 수
there you go okay that's looking kind of
거기서 너 괜찮아 질 거야.
nice let's go back there again and bring
좋아, 다시 거기로 가서 다시 가져와.
it down to all I'm doing is I'm
내가하는 모든 일에 이르기 까지 나는
desaturating the image a little bit
이미지를 약간 채도를 떨어 뜨리는
let's bring it down to seven I'm gonna
나는거야의 일곱로 끌어 내릴 수 있도록
get to 71 I earn a 69 to 71 try that so
71에 도달 하면 69에서 71까지 벌어들입니다 .
what happened what ends up happening is
무슨 일이 일어난 일인지는
is you get this softer kind of tone to
너는이 부드러운 톤의 톤을 얻는거야?
the image which is has more of a film
더 많은 이미지를 가진 이미지
quality to it it's a little bit less
그것에 조금 더 적은 품질
saturation digital cameras really have a
채도 디지털 카메라에는 실제로
you know high saturation level this kind
당신 은 높은 채도 레벨 을 알고 있습니다.
of softens it just a little bit and you
조금 부드럽게 하고 너는
can you can play with that I've brought
내가 가져온 것을 가지고 놀 수 있니?
it down awfully low there might bring it
그것은 그것을 가져올지도 모르다.
up just a little bit but to be able to
조금까지하지만 할 수 있도록
make those kind of manipulations without
그 종류의 조작을하지 않고
having to go into post so that means I
게시물 에 들어가야 한다는 의미는
can do this in Telestream Wirecast
Telestream Wirecast 에서이 작업을 수행 할 수 있습니다.
and I'm doing it on the fly and I can
나는 그것을 비행 중에하고 있고 나는 할 수있다.
change it like that and make my picture
그런 식으로 변경하고 내 그림을
look great so that when I record to disc
디스크에 녹음 할 때
which is exactly what I'm doing right oh
정확히 내가 옳은 일을하는 거지.
I'm out of focus but there it is there's
초점이 맞지 않지만 거기에
the record then I don't have to then
기록은 그때 그때 필요가 없습니다
take it into an editor sweet and recolor
달콤하고 색다른 에디터로 가져 가라.
eyes and fix it up so there you have it
눈과 그것을 고칠 수 있도록 거기에 당신 이 그것을
I think that's a great a great
나는 그것이 위대 하다고 생각 한다.
additional feature as well as the fact
추가 기능뿐만 아니라 사실
that I can make it so that I'm not 20
내가 20 세가되지 않도록 내가 만들 수있다.
pounds heavier like the black magic card
검은 마법 카드 처럼 무겁다.
would do to me so there you have it
너는 거기에 그렇게 할거야.
folks take care thanks for watching and
사람들이보고에 대한 치료 감사를 타고
I look forward so much I can't wait to
기다릴 수 없을만큼 많이 기다려집니다.
show you the show show and I hope that
당신에게 쇼 쇼를 보여 나는 희망
you'll be along for the ride so we'll
너는 타기 위해 함께 있을거야 그래서 우리는
talk to you soon bye bye
안녕히 곧 이야기